For God's sakes, Sheldon,
you are driving me crazy.
Your anger is not with me,
but with mathematics.
I'm pretty sure my anger is with you.
What is happening to us?
We're falling apart.
- Who are you calling?
- The only man who can restore...
(Sheldon:)...any semblance of balance
to our universe.
HOWARD [ON RECORDING]:
This is Howard.
CHRISTY [ON RECORDING]
This is Christy.
HOWARD: We can't get to the phone
right now because we're having sex.
CHRISTY: You're not gonna put that
on your message, are you?
HOWARD:
I'm just kidding. I'll re-record it.
[BEEPS]
(Leonard:)Sheldon, think this through.
(Leonard:)You're going to ask Howard
to choose between sex and "Halo."
(Sheldon:)No, I'm going to ask him
to choose between sex and "Halo 3."
(Sheldon:)As far as I know,
sex has not been upgraded...
...to include hi-def graphics
and enhanced weapon systems.
(Leonard:)You're right, all sex has is nudity,
orgasms and human contact.
(Sheldon:)My point.